時は戦国、乱世の時代。
からくり人の住むジパング国では群雄割拠して合戦に明け暮れ、
からくり武芸者たちも勝利と栄光を目指してしのぎを削っていた。
そしていま、からくり武芸者ナンバー１を目指す、とてつもないヒーローが誕生した！
ムサシ、見参でござるだス！
からくり剣豪伝ムサシロード
男はいつでも　世界の真ん中で
いちばん　強くなる日を
AH! AH! 夢見て
心の刃　大空にふりかざし
冒険の旅の　幕を開ける
ジパング国を　さすらう剣豪
その名　からくりびと　ムサシ
GO! FIGHT!
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　昨日よりも　今日　強い
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
明日は　輝くぞ
鍔迫り合いの音が
眩しい人生
戦い　思い切りと　静けさと
BUGEI! 二刀流　ムサシ
みけんが　きらめいた　ムサシ！！
죽었다 생각됐던 한조는 의문의 일족 시라누이와 손을 잡아 다시 이에야스의 명줄을 노린다.
Hanzō was thought to be dead, but he joined hands with mysterious Shianui clan and is looking to kill Ieyasu again.
이에야스의 암살을 미연에 방지한 무사시 일행은 남겨진 지도를 단서로
Musashi and others has managed to prevent Ieyasu from being assassinated, and according to the map that Hanzō dropped,
한조를 쓰러뜨리기 위해 규슈에 여행을 떠났다.
they go on a journey to Kyushu to take Hanzō down.
사이고 씨는
수수께끼의 인물이오
Mr. Saigo is
a Mysterious Person
(시나가와슈쿠: 일본의 역참 중 하나로 에도 사(4)숙의 하나
사츠마 국(國): 사이카이도에 있던 일본의 옛 율령국)
(Shinagawa-shuku: shuku is a type of historical Japanese station/inn, and Shinagawa-shuku was one of the Four Edo Inns
Satsuma-kuni: A past province in Saikai Circuit, now Kagoshima)
여긴 시나가와슈쿠. 무사시 일행은 여기서 규슈의 사츠마니아 행 배를 타고자 하고 있었다.
This is Shinagawa-juku. Musashi and others are going to get a boat ride to Satsumania at Kyushu.
그렇지만!
But!
뭣이오, 이번 배는 밤에 떠나오... 그럼 조금 더 느긋하게 먹었으면 좋았을 걸 그랬소.
The next boat departs in night-dasu... I should have eaten my last meal slower if I knew that-dasu...
흥, 오래 전부터 그러지. 성질 급한 무예가는 보기 흉하다고.
Hmph, do you know what they say from the past? A martial artist who rushes is unsightly.
넌 맨날 떠나기 직전이 되서야 우당탕탕 거리니 말이지.
You always make a big fuss right before you have to go out.
지금까지 맨날 그랬던 너 말이다.
You were like that ever since I met you.
좀, 무사시, 창피하니까 일어나!
Hey, Musashi, you're embarassing me! Get up!
그런 소리를 해도, 나 서둘렀으니까 밥도 못 먹어서...
No matter what you say, I couldn't eat my meal since I was in hurry...
모르는 사람 치자.
Let's treat him as if we don't know him.
오센짱도 차가워...
Osenchan is cold too...
자, 자, 개점 서비스인 단고 빨리 먹기 콩쿠르입니다!
People, I'm holding a dango quick eating contest as a shop opening event!
뭐라?! 단고 빨리 먹기?!
What?! Dango quick eating contest?!
이럴 때만은 잽싸다니까.
He's so quick only at times like this.
오픈
OPEN
자, 단고 빨리 먹기 콩쿠르입니다! 누구 도전할 사람 없나요!
Welcome to dango quick eating contest! Would anybody want to attempt?
이 모래시계의 모래가 떨어질 때까지 단고 100줄을 먹으면 값은 무료.
If you eat 100 lines of dango before this hourglass runs out, it's free!
덤으로, 300문의 용돈도 받습니다!
You're also gonna get 300 mons in addition!
자, 누구 해 볼 사람 없습니까!
Any participants?
내가 도전하오!
I'll try that-dasu!
무사시. 네가 왜 여기에?!
Musashi! Why are you here?!
어? 나 알고 있소?
Huh? Do you know me-dasu?
글쎄, 난 너같은 잘생긴 아이는 처음 보네!
Well, I never saw a handsome boy like you until now!
역시 그렇소.
I knew it-dasu!
그렇고말고!
Yeah, right!
그럼 잘 먹겠소! 팍팍 가지고 오시오!
Then let me eat-dasu! Bring it on-dasu!
그, 그럼 시작합니다.
T- then let's begin.
준비, 땅!
Ready, go!
다음!
Next!
무예가 주제에 되는 한껏 창피한 놈이군.
For a martial artist, he's trying his best to be disgraceful.
힘내, 무사시! 상금 받으면 축하로 다 같이 단고 먹자!
You can do it, Musashi! Let's have a dango party if you win!
제기랄, 잘도 쳐먹네!
Damn, he's such an extreme eater!
진짜, 이렇게는 힘들게 연 가게까지 먹혀버리겠네!
He'll even eat up my store that I manged to open at last!
어이, 좀만 더 먹으면 100줄이야!
Hey, you're almost there!
이렇게 된 바 최후의 수단이다!
This leaves me no choice!
(텐구: 얼굴이 붉고 코가 높으며/길며 하늘을 날 수 있다는 상상의 괴물. 과거 동양인의 서양인(유럽인) 얼굴 표현.)
(Tengu: An imaginary monster that has a long/high nose and a red face, and can fly. A depiction of Western/European people.)
어! 텐구가 나무에 부딪혀서 코피 흘리고 있어!
Look! A Tengu has hit a tree and it's nosebleeding!
어디, 어디?!
Where, where?!
이걸로 300문은 내 것!
And now 300 mons are mine!
네, 거기까지!
And that's it!
자, 시간이 다 됐어요.
Look, time's up!
어라, 아까까진 아직 많이 남아 있었다고 생각했는데...
Huh, I thought it still had a lot to go just before...
네, 안타깝습니다! 다 먹지 못한 사람에게선 300문을 가져갑니다!
Well, that's too bad for you! I'll take 300 mons from whoever couldn't eat 'em all!
어, 300문?! 나, 나, 돈 내야 한다고는 못 들었소...
What, 300 mons?! I never heard I had to pay for that...
무슨 소릴! 다 못 먹으면 돈 내는 건 상식이잖아요?
What are you talking about? It's obvious that you have to pay if you couldn't eat them all!
어이, 돈 내쇼.
Hey, give me your money.
나, 그런 큰 돈 없소...
I don't have that much money-dasu...
아, 코지로!
Hey, Kojirō!
미안하지만 돈 빌려주면 좋겠소!
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your money-dasu?
거절한다.
I refuse.
에, 왜이오?
Hey, why is that-dasu?
그런 빨리 먹기 대회 따위에 나간 네 잘못이다.
This is all your fault, for participating in a quick eating competition.
알아서 해.
You take care of this.
그런! 괜찮지 않소?
Please! Isn't it a good enough-dasu?
저기, 저기, 저기, 저기?
Hey, hey, hey, hey?
어리광 피우지 마라.
Don't act like a brat.
치. 구두쇠.
Tch. Cheapskate.
구두쇠라고?!
Cheapskate?!
순 구두쇠!
Base cheapskate!
(do-kechi)
순 구두쇠?!
Base cheapskate?!
난 노랭이라고 불리는 게 이 세상에서 제일 싫다! 그걸로 모자라서 순을 붙여?!
I despise being called a cheapskate more than everything else in this world! And then you put base(do-) there?!
구두쇠니까 구두쇠라고 말할 뿐이오!
I'm telling you're a cheapskate because you are one-dasu!
또 그 소리 했겠다! 이 숙맥!
You said that again, you dumbass(doji)!
"숙"을 붙였겠소, "숙"을!
You dared to put bass(do) there!
어이, 내라면 내!
Hey, just pay, will you?!
아, 저 그게...
Uh, you know...
낼 필요는 없다.
No need to pay-gowasu.
뭐야, 넌!
Who the heck are you?!
난 사이고라 하는 자다.
My name is Saigo-gowasu.
사이고
Saigo
아까부터 보고 있었고 자네는 꾀를 부리고 있다.
I was looking at you for a while, and I know you're cheating-gowasu.
이, 이상한 소리 마라! 어디에 그런 증거가 있냐!
D- don't fool around! You have no evidence for that!
아, 저 모래시계!
Hey, that hourglass!
-어, 어?
-잘도 속였겠소!
-Huh, huh?!
-You fooled me!
아, 하지 마!
Hey, don't do that!
아, 너는 지라이얀!
Hey, you must be Jiraiyan!
들켰으니 어쩔 수 없군! 안녕이다, 무사시!
As you've found out, it can't be helped! That's bye to you, Musashi!
아, 멈추시오, 지라이얀!
Hey, stop, Jiraiyan!
젠장, 다음에 보면 혼쭐내 주겠소!
Damn! I'll take it out on you next time I see you-dasu!
도와 주어서 정말 고맙소.
Thank you so much for helping.
아무렴 좋다. 난 부정한 일은 몹시 싫으니 속는 모습을 그대로 두고 볼 수는 없었다.
No problem-gowasu. I despise dishonest things, so I couldn't just watch people being deceived-gowasu.
자, 우리도 가자.
Let's go, too.
왕짠돌이.
Base cheapskate.
어? 왜 그래, 둘 다.
You two, what happened?
나, 이런 박정한 놈하고는 더는 같이 여행하고 싶지 않소.
I do not want to travel with a cruel bastard like him anymore-dasu.
저도 이런 경박한 자와 함께 있는 건 자존심이 용서하지 못합니다.
My pride also do not forgive me from being with a fickle guy like this.
경박한 자라? 그 쪽이야말로 박정한 구두쇠이오!
Fickle?! You are even more cruel and cheap!
또 그 소리 했겠다, 이게!
How dare you say that again?!
에휴, 너희들 지금 싸우고 있을 때가 아니잖아? 우린 이제 막 적의 본거지에 쳐들어가려던 참이잖아!
You guys! It's not a time for you to quarrel! We are about to penetrate into the base of the enemy!
시라누이 일족 따위 나하고는 관계 없소! 내 목표는 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 되는 일 뿐이오!
That Shiranui Clan has nothing to do with me-dasu! My only objective is to become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
나도 그렇다!
Same for me too!
아, 그러셔? 너희 그럴 생각이었네? 그래! 이제 너희 따위는!
Oh, is that so? So that was your ulterior motive! I see! You guys do not matter to me anymore!
혼자 사츠마니아에 쳐들어가서 시라누이 일족 전멸시켜 줄 테니까!
I'll go Satsumania by myself and annihilate Shiranui Clan all by myself!
흥!
Hmph!
아, 기다려 주십시오, 센히메 님!
Please wait, Senhime!
히메!
Hime!
흥.
Hmph.
공주님!
Princess!
공주님, 공주님! 기다려 주세요! 아까 말은 오는 말에 가는 말이었습니다!
Princess, princess! Please wait for me! That before was nothing more than tit for tat!
절대 본심이 아닙니다!
I was not serious when I was saying that!
시끄러워. 끈덕지게 따라오지 마!
Be quiet. Just don't follow me like that!
기다려 주세요, 센히메 님!
Please wait, Senhime!
치한이야!
A pervert!
어, 치한?
What, a pervert?
어디? 치한이라고?
What? A pervert?
너냐! 그 자식이!
So you are a pervert!
-어...
-아앍! 살려줘! 변태야, 이 남자 놈!
-Err...
-Help! This guy is a pervert!
아니아니아니, 저는 치한이 아닙니다.
Nononono, I'm not a pervert!
-치한이 아닙...
-거짓말쟁이! 음란한 생각하다간 대머리 된다!
-I'm not a pervert...
-You liar! You're gonna get bald if you act like that!
얌전히 따라와라!
Be obedient and follow us!
그, 그만둬! 치, 치한 아니야! 그만, 그만!
S- stop! I'm not a pervert! Stop, stop!
센히메 님!
Senhime!
뭐야, 뭐야, 뭐야! 걔들도 참, 저런 녀석들한테 보호받지 않아도 충분히 혼자서 시라누이 일족 따위 때려눕혀 주겠어!
What were they thinking?! I'll show that I don't need their protection as I can take Shiranui Clan down by myself!
어이, 서둘러라! 여기다!
Hey, hurry up! This way!
어이어이, 서둘러라, 서둘러!
Hurry up, hurry!
저건 시라누이 닌자?
That must be a ninja of Shiranui.
시라누이
SHIRANUI
쟤들 뭘 옮기는 걸까?
I wonder what they are carrying.
위험
DANGER
이, 이건...
N- no way...
칫, 뭣이오, 뭣이오! 오센짱도 코지로도! 쉽사리 화내는 놈들은 난 싫소!
Tch, what are wrong with Osenchan and Kojirō-dasu?! I hate whoever gets angry so easily-dasu!
그래도... 괜찮을지 모르겠소. 시라누이 일족은 강적이라 하고...
But still... I'm worried-dasu. Shiranui Clan is told to be a strong enemy, too.
아니아니, 나하고는 관계 없는 일이오.
No, that has nothing to do with me-dasu.
나는 지팡구 제일의 무예가가 될 목표가 있소!
I have an objective to become the number one martial artist of Jipangu!
아! 사이고 씨!
Hey! Mr. Saigo!
어?!
Wha-?!
이건 시라누이의 문장이오!
This is Shiranui's coat-dasu!
이건 수상하오.
There's something with this-dasu.
손님, 하나 어떠십니까?
Mister, would you like one?
어디 보자.
Let me see.
오, 이건 꽤 진귀한 것이군.
This is an exquisite one-gowasu.
역시 안목이 있으십니다.
You have an eye for these.
그래서 그 쪽하고는 연락이 되었나?
So, could you get into contact with him-gowasu?
예, 그 곳에서 기다린다고 하셨습니다.
Yessir. He said he's waiting at that place.
그렇군.
I see.
이 접시를 먹이접시로 할까, 시로?
Would you like to use this dish as your bowl, Shiro?
하하하, 그래, 마음에 안 드는구나.
Hahaha, I see. You don't like it-gowasu.
-그럼 다음 기회에.
-예, 그리 알지요!
-Maybe next time, then-gowasu.
-Understood!
점점 수상해지오.
It's getting even more suspicious-dasu.
센히메 님!
Senhime!
센히메 님! 센히메 님!
Senhime! Senhime!
이 자식! 이 나를 누구라 생각하나!
Hey! Who do you think I am?!
제너럴 이에야스의 손녀 센히메다! 당장 포승을 풀어라!
I am the granddaughter of General Ieyasu, Senhime! Release me this instance!
허, 잡혀 있는 주제에 활기찬 여자군.
Aren't you a vigorous girl, for being captured.
이 날 어쩔 셈이야?
What are you going to do to me?
저 짐을 본 이상 살아서 돌아갈 수는 없아.
As you've seen the load over there, you will not go back alive.
시멘트 덩이로 만들어서 에도 만에 가라앉혀 주겠다.
We'll make you into a lump of cement and sink into Edo Bay.
어?
What?!
자기들끼리 분열해버린 무사시 일행.
Musashi and others has split among friends.
과연 센히메의 명은, 그리고 수수께끼의 사내 사이고의 정체는?
Will Senhime Survive? And what about the mysterious man Saigo?
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
이렇게 보고 있으면 전혀 악인으로는 안 보이오...
He doesn't look like a bad guy at all-dasu...
역시 수상하오.
Really suspicious-dasu.
누구냐!
Who's there-gowasu?
야옹... 야옹...
meow... meow...
고양이군.
A cat, eh?
야옹...
meow...
센히메 님!
Senhime!
대체 어디에 가 버렸나...
Where did she disappear to?
시라누이
SHIRANUI
저건 분명 시라누이의 문장.
That is Shiranui's coat.
저만큼의 무기를 어디에 가져간다는 거야?
Where are you transporting all those weapons to?
흥, 죽을 주제에 그런 걸 알아봤자 소용없지.
Hmph, that information won't help you since you're going to die.
죽을 거니까 알려줘도 상관 없잖아?
And that's why you can tell me the reason!
뭐, 그것도 그렇지. 듣고 놀라라! 사츠마니아에!
Well, that makes sense! Listen and be surprised! To Satsumania!
사츠마니아에 가져가서 어쩌려고?
And what are you going to do with these at Satsumania?
흥, 뻔한 일을. 지팡국을 수중에 넣기 위해서 사츠마니아 정복으로 시작하는 것이지.
Hmph, isn't that obvious? Taking over Satsumania will be the first step of taking over the whole Jipangu.
뭐라고? 그런 건 이 센히메가 용서 못한다!
What?! I, Senhime, cannot forgive that!
허, 손발도 꼼짝 못하는 주제에 뭘 할 수 있단 거냐?
Why don't you explain what can you do when you can't move?
두고 봐라. 지금 너희들이 어떻게 되어도 몰라. 소중한 동료가 구해주러 올 테니까!
Just you see. Anything can happen to you guys, since my precious comrades are coming to save me!
헤, 그 전에 넌 시멘트덩이다!
Hmph, you'll become a cement lump before that!
무사시! 코지로!
Musashi! Kojirō!
누구냐!
Who's that?!
센히메 님. 구하러 왔습니다.
Senhime. I'm here to save you!
코지로!
Kojirō!
에잇, 우리에게 대들다니 건방지다!
How impudent of you, trying to defy us?!
잡아라!
Get him!
비검 츠바메가에시!
Secret sword! Tsubamegaeshi!
거기까지다, 꼬맹아!
That's as far as you go, you brat!
뭐야?!
What?!
츠바메가에시가 어떤 기술이든 이걸 이길 수는 없지.
Whatever Tsubamegaeshi is, it can't defeat this.
비겁하다!
That's cowardly!
자, 순순히 칼을 내려놓아라.
Put your sword down like a good boy.
코지로!
Kojirō!
젠장!
Damn!
이거 원, 잘 걷는 사람이오. 난 이미 발에 감각이 없소.
That person surely walks well-dasu. I don't feel my legs already-dasu.
후후, 드디어 동료하고 만나오.
Finally you're joining your comrades-dasu.
사이고 씨는 어디 있을까나...
I wonder where Mr. Saigo is...
그대가 말하는 대로 이대로는 지팡구 국에 안 좋습니다.
Just as you're saying, Jipangu will be wasted at this rate-gowasu.
사이고 씨!
Mr. Saigo!
그걸 위해서도 이 세상의 체제를 바꾸어야!
For that too, the system of the world must be changed!
뭣이오?!
What-dasu?!
그럼 당신.
Then, you...
사이고 씨, 각오!
Prepare yourself, Mr. Saigo!
사이고 씨, 당신이라는 자는!
Mr. Saigo, who are you?!
그대는 낮에 단고 군이군. 이상한 곳에서 튀어나와 뭔 짓이냐!
You are that dango boy I saw during the day-gowasu. What are you doing, springing out from a weird place-gowasu?!
나, 당신, 좋은 사람이라 생각했지만 시라누이의 동료라니 놀랐소!
I thought you were a good guy, but I was surprised when I realized you are Shiranui's comrade-dasu!
자, 잠깐만, 단고 군. 난 그대가 뭔 말을 하고 있는지 전혀 모르겠다.
J- just a moment, dango guy-gowasu. I do not get what you're talking about at all-gowasu.
에잇, 이 마당에 와서 아직 시치미 뗄 생각이오! 깨끗히 죽지 못하는 놈이오!
Are you still trying to play innocent at the last moment-dasu?! Know when to give up-dasu!
각오!
Prepare yourself!
무사시 군, 관둬라!
Musashi, stop!
료, 료마 씨!
M- Mr. Ryoma!
오랜만이다, 무사시 군.
It's been a while, Musashi.
어? 사이고 씨는 사츠마니아의 영주였소!
What?! So Mr. Saigo was feudal lord of Satsumania!
그런 높으신 분으로는 안 보였소!
You didn't look like one-dasu!
나도 되고 싶어서 되고 싶은 건 아니다. 그러니까 보통은 이런 가벼운 차림을 하고 있지.
I am not a lord because I wanted to be-gowasu. That's why I usually go with a light clothing-gowasu.
그래도 료마 씨한테 그런 높은 분이 방문하다니 놀랐소!
But still, I am surprised to know someone that venerable is visiting Mr. Ryoma!
난 료마 씨의 새 지팡구 국을 만드려는 덧없는 아이디어에 홀딱 반해서 말이지.
I am totally charmed by Mr. Ryoma's idea of making the new Jipangu.
그래도, 나는 무사시 군이 아는 대로 수배자니까, 그렇게 간단히 만날 수는 없었지.
But as you know, Musashi, I am a wanted man, and I couldn't meet him that easily.
거기에 상인이나 농사꾼으로 변장한 정보원과 연락해서 겨우 만나게 된 거다.
Moreover, I could meet him thanks to secret agents disguised as merchants and farmers-gowasu.
그랬소. 그것도 모르고 실례를 저질렀소.
So that was what's it about-dasu. I apologize for my discourtesy-dasu.
괜찮아, 괜찮아! 누구도 실수할 수 있지.
It's alright, it's alright! Anybody can make mistakes-gowasu.
그래도, 무사시 군은 아까 날 시라누이의 동료라고 했는데, 그건 어떤 뜻이었나?
But still, you thought I was a comrade of Shiranui, and what did you exactly mean by that-gowasu?
그러니까, 낮에 사이고 씨가 시라누이의 문장이 적힌 종이를 떨어뜨려서...
It's because you dropped a paper with Shiranui's emblem on it back in afternoon, Mr. Saigo.
그건 시라누이 일족을 찾을 단서이다.
That is a key to finding Shiranui Clan-gowasu.
사이고 씨도 시라누이 일족을 찾고 있었소?!
Were you looking for Shiranui Clan too-dasu?
그래. 사실은 내 성의 금고가 시라누이 일족에게 털려서...
Yes. To be honest, the treasure house of my castle has been robbed by Shiranui Clan.
훔친 돈이 이 에도토피아에 옮겨진 것 같다.
It seems that the stolen money has been transferred to Edotopia-gowasu.
그래서 나는 료마 씨와 만나는 김에 훔쳐진 돈을 찾고자 하고 있었다.
And I was trying to take the stolen money back, taking this opportunity of meeting Mr. Ryoma-gowasu.
우리가 분쟁 없는 지팡구 국을 만들고자 하고 있는데 용서할 수 없는 놈들이지.
Those are unforgivable ones, especially since we're trying to make Jipangu State without disputes.
정말이오. 그러나 대체 어디에 있을지.
You're right. But we do not know where they are...
시라누이 일족이라면 항구의 창고에 있다.
Those Shiranui Clan guys are in the warehouse at the port.
지라이얀!
Jiraiyan!
또 뉘우침없이 나타났겠소!
You incorrigibly showed yourself again-dasu!
날 신경 쓸 틈이 있으면 창고에나 서둘러라! 코지로하고 센히메가 어떻게 되어도 난 모른다!
If you have time to care about me, then go to the warehouse! I don't know what'll happen to Kojirō and Senhime!
뭣이오?!
What-dasu?!
이걸로 낮에 건 갚았다. 그럼!
Now that I've paid back that from the daytime, farewell!
항구의 창고?
The warehouse at the port?
사츠마니아 행 배가 왔다!
The ship to Satsumania is here!
좋아! 바로 짐을 실어라. 그리고 누가 이 둘을 빠뜨리고 와라!
Great! Ship those cargo, and someone go sink these two!
예!
Yessir!
싫어싫어! 이런 곳에서 가라앉고 싶지 않아!
No, no! I don't want to sink at a place like this!
이렇게 된 바 조용히 죽음을 맞이합시다.
Let's face our death, as it can't be helped.
그래도 에도 만 같은 더러운 바다에 빠지는 건 내 프라이드가 용서할 수 없다!
But my pride cannot forgive me from being sunken into a dirty sea like Edo Bay!
하다못해 하와이같은 아름다운 바다에 빠뜨려 줘!
Drop me into a beautiful sea like Hawaii, at least!
무사시! 여기서 구하러 안 오면 귀신이 되어서 널 잡겠어!
Musashi! If you don't come save us here, then we'll become ghosts and haunt you!
자, 바다에 던져라!
Throw them into sea!
예!
Yessir!
멈추시오!
Stop right there-dasu!
누, 누구냐?!
W- who's there?!
하늘이 알고 땅이 안다! 너희들의 악은!
The sky knows and the ground knows about your evil!
이 무사시가 용서하지 않겠소!
I, Musashi, will not forgive you-dasu!
무사시!
Musashi!
뭘 건방지게! 잡아라!
How impudent of you! Get him!
고마워, 무사시!
Thank you, Musashi!
뭘 꾸물꾸물대냐! 저 송사리같은 둘은 바로 처리해 버려라!
Don't you know what to do?! Get rid of those two!
뭐, 뭐야?!
W- what?!
너, 너희들은 누구냐!
W- who's there?!
분쟁 없는 지팡구 국을 만드려는 자다!
We are the ones to make Jipangu State free of disputes!
료마 씨! 사이고 씨!
Mr. Ryoma! Mr. Saigo!
웃기고 있네. 다들 한꺼번에 몰아 처리해 주겠다!
Don't make us laugh! We'll take you down all at once!
체스트!
Chest!
보고 느끼거라! 지겐류 기합술!
Watch and feel! Jigen Style Shout Technique!
네놈들 같은 놈들이 규슈에 있다고 생각하니 난 맹렬하게 슬프다!
To think that bastards like you are in Kyushu, that makes me sad to the level of infuriating-gowasu!
체스트!
Chest!
츠바메가에시!
Tsubamegaeshi!
료마 씨! 저 창고 안에 무기가 가득 있어! 빨리 어떻게 해!
Mr. Ryoma! That warehouse is full of weapons! Do something!
맡기쇼!
Leave it to me!
만세!
Hooray!
도망쳐라, 도망쳐!
Run away, run!
아, 마침 적당하게 구할 수 있어서 다행이었소, 오센짱, 코지로!
It is a big relief that we could rescue you in time-dasu, Osenchan and Kojirō!
흥! 이런 꼴이 된 것도 애초에 네놈이 단고 빨리 먹기를 해서 그런 것이다!
Hmph! This also is because you ate dangos quickly at the first place!
뭣이오?!
What-dasu?!
-이것도 다-
-니들 작작 좀해!
-This is all-
-That's enough, stop it!
사츠마니아를 공격하려고 하는 시라누이 일족의 음모는 일단 쳐부수었다.
The plot of Shiranui Clan to attack Satsumania has been dealt with for now.
그렇지만 무사시와 코지로 사이에는 아직 마음의 응어리가 남아 있다.
But an ill feeling is still between Musashi and Kojirō.
파란만장의 일행을 태운 배는 이대로 규슈에 간다.
The ship with stormy ones full of dramas aboard is heading to Kyushu.
적진에 쳐들어가는 무사시 일행의 운명은 어찌 되는가!
What will be the destiny of Musashi and others, making an inroad on the enemy?
カラのポケットに　ツキが
飛び込むことも　あるさ
おっきな声で　笑えば
あしたには　朝が来る
無くすものなんか　何もないさ
やっちゃえ！イケイケ！
手ぶらは　強いぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
人生　てなもんさ　チャンスが　ほら
しっぽを振って　追ってくるぜ
てなもんだ　のーてんきに行こう
未来も　てなもんさ　あしたが　ほら
両手ひろげて　笑ってるぜ
규슈의 사츠마니아에 상륙한 나는 히미코 씨라는 예쁘고 친절한 사람하고 만났소.
After landing to Satsumania at Kyushu, I met with a person named Satsumania, who is pretty and kind-dasu.
마치 엄마같소!
She's just like a mother-dasu!
그러나 시라누이 일족의 함정에 빠진 나는 무슨, 진검승부의 무예 대회에서 벤케이하고 싸우게 되오!
But I fall into the trap of Shinarui Clan,
and I had to fight against Benkei in a martial art competition of fighting with real swords!
다음 이야기! 나, 비뚤어지오!
Next story! I Become Delinquent!
질풍노도의 엄마! 이오!
It's a stormy mommy! -dasu!
다음 이야기
나
비뚤어지오
기대하세요!
Next Episode
I
Become Delinquent
Look forwards for it!